<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://holdenlim.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://holdenlim.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-03-08T02:22:11+00:00</updated><id>https://holdenlim.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>Driven self-directed high school student with a passion for technology and programming seeking hands-on experience in computer science and software development. Also interested in any opportunities related to data science. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hello everyone!</title><link href="https://holdenlim.github.io/blog/2024/hello/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello everyone!"/><published>2024-02-29T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2024-02-29T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://holdenlim.github.io/blog/2024/hello</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://holdenlim.github.io/blog/2024/hello/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="welcome">Welcome!</h2> <p>To my all-new web site. To commemorate this occasion, I am answering a selection of Frequently Asked Questions which have never been asked to me ever in my life.</p> <h5 id="why-would-you-make-a-site-like-this">Why would you make a site like this?</h5> <p>I want to have a link that I can give people to contact me for business purposes. This website has some info about me, and I’m going to publish my resume onto here soon. I might also use the blog feature to post comics, short stories, and drawings.</p> <h5 id="i-see-youre-using-al-folio-isnt-that-for-professors-and-stuff">I see you’re using al-folio. Isn’t that for professors and stuff?</h5> <p>That’s correct. I am not a professor of any sort, nor will I become one at any point in the near future. However, this theme meets all my needs and then some. I had to remove pages like students and teaching material, but otherwise it works and looks great.</p> <h5 id="what-is-the-point-of-an-faq-when-no-one-has-ever-asked-you-a-question">What is the point of an FAQ when no one has ever asked you a question?</h5> <p>That’s the best part. There’s not. I’m mainly just testing out the blog aspect of al-folio.</p> <p>Well, that’s the end of my first blog post. I may return soon, or I may never return. I have absolutely no idea.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[First post]]></summary></entry></feed>